<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brycen Buckingham</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brycen Buckingham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Interest in Python</title>
      <link>/blog/my-interest-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/my-interest-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Hey Y’all,
Thanks for tuning-in to another blog post! I just wanted to take some time to express my thoughts and interest in working with Python.
This semester (Fall 2019) is actually the first time that I’ve used or worked with Python. Previously, I’ve used RStudio and R to explore statistical relationships within data sets, but I’m now dipping my toes into something that’s new to me. So far, I’ve really fallen in love with Regular Expression Applications and analyzing DNA sequences with the Needleman-Wunsch and Smith-Walterman Algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume as of December 2019</title>
      <link>/resume/resume-as-of-december-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/resume-as-of-december-2019/</guid>
      <description>Click here to see a pdf version of my resume
Brycen Buckinghambrycenbuckingham@gmail.com
2400 Nueces St. Unit 1302 ∙ Austin, TX 78712 ∙ (408) 881-2539
EDUCATIONThe University of Texas at Austin
Bachelor of Science and Arts, Biology
Certificate in Business of HealthcareMay 2020
Overall GPA: 3.49
EXPERIENCE2400 Nueces Apartments - Marketing Manager
Austin, Texas | March 2018 - Current
- Presented our community to potential residents through digital platforms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my Website</title>
      <link>/blog/welcome-to-my-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/welcome-to-my-website/</guid>
      <description>Dear Readers/Viewers,
Welcome to my website! I’m so excited that you’re here and reading this post. I will be using this website to document the happenings in my life, as well as the various projects I’ve worked on. At the moment, I’m just starting off with my coding career, so conent may be limited. But, before I discredit myself, let me tell you a little about who I am!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are two projects I worked on during my senior year at the University of Texas at Austin
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1 - US Beers Final</title>
      <link>/project1beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1beer/</guid>
      <description>Dataset Choice
When searching for datasets to work with, I came across these two sets on kaggle.com. As a beer fan myself, Ithought that these ones would be fun to work with! They feature beers and breweries from all across the UnitedStates. The author scrapped and compiled these from a website called CraftCans using python. He included thefollowing variables:
The name of the brewery and it’s location (state and city)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2 - Body Fat</title>
      <link>/project2bdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2bdf/</guid>
      <description>Brycen Buckingham - blb3757Project 2: Exploration of Body Fat MeasuresThe dataset that I chose comes from the Journal of Statistics Education, and it explores many variables that one might use to predict an individual’s body fat percentage as well as the distribution of said fat around the body.The data set observed 252 males of varying height, weight, and age to gather this data. There are 17 naitive variables that the researchers included, which are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>